I don't know about y'all, but in my personal life, I feel like I've spent a lot of time
trying not to require too much, not to require too much emotionally from my friends, from
my partners, from my family, you know, because I guess probably early on, I realized that
like there wasn't much that could be given and that if you require too much, then people
feel some type of way, right? I've lost friends because I wanted them to call me back and
was like, Hey, like, I, I don't know why you're not calling me back. And then it's like, Oh,
you're too demanding. Right. So, and I've always been like a super hyper tapped in and person
to my emotions. And so I feel like I somehow became conscious of like, okay, so if you just
don't require too much, then like people won't leave you. But the reality is people leave
you, people leave you for a myriad of reasons, but ultimately like what is too much? And I
think when you start examining that, you start to realize that for the most part, this is
a world that isn't emotionally available. So even wanting just like the basics is a lot,
let alone being very tapped in. But I decided recently in like the past couple of years that
I'm just going to ask for what I am, for what I give. And that those who are down for that,
they stay down. And those who aren't, they stay distant. And it works out for anybody.
But in case you're wondering, um, you know, like wanting things like accountability,
wanting things like responsiveness, wanting things like reciprocal, uh, attentiveness, uh,
for, you know, life, lifing, um, you know, just kind of wanting things like quality time,
wanting things like self-awareness, you know, compassion. Um,
these are things that I don't think a lot of us allow ourselves to want because we're told that
it is too much to expect this from people, but it is not. And it's absolutely not too much
when you expect it from yourself. Get what you give.